adirect2z.com 2008-12-18

# Privacy Policy

## Definitions

"The Owners" means Yvonne Arlott.

## Introduction

"The Owners" consider issues relating to your privacy to be a serious matter. As such, "The Owners" have created and implemented this Privacy Policy so that you understand what "The Owners" may and may not do with certain personal information. "The Owners" encourage you to review this Privacy Policy.

## What information do we collect?

On some parts of the website we may ask you to register, and if you do we may ask for your name, company names, addresses, telephone numbers, fax numbers, e-mail addresses and specific business interests and some other personal information. We may also use cookies.

For an explanation, see the section on cookies below.

## Use of cookies

Cookies are a unique identifier that is sent to your Internet browser. The Internet browser may then store the cookie on your hard drive. Cookies can be used to track a visitor to a website as the visitor navigates the website and to store information. They can inform the website what pages you visit, when you last visited and your preferences, which enable websites to provide you with a more personalised service. If a visitor requests a specific language is used, a cookie will be used to record this information so that the visitor does not need to specify his or her language preference for each web page that is delivered to the visitor's browser. You can set your browser to refuse cookies, or to warn you before accepting them. We may use cookies, but most parts of our site can be accessed even if your cookies are turned off.

## Uses of Information

We use the information to help us understand more about how our website is used and to improve our site. "The Owners" only use personal information for the purpose for which it was provided and certain other activities, which are reasonably ancillary to such purpose. For example, if you send us an e-mail with a question or comment, "The Owners" will use your e-mail address to respond to you. Also, "The Owners" may store your e-mail and e-mail address and a copy of our response for future reference. "The Owners" may also use and disclose personal information that is relevant to a legal proceeding or as required by law.

## Do we share information?

We do not sell your personal information to others. Some of our products are hosted by third parties but we agree with those third parties that they will keep your information secure and not use it for other purposes. If you sign up for services that are managed or offered by other organisations, they will obtain your information. A number of other people's websites have links on our site. If you link to their sites, they may collect information. Such sites are not within our control and are not covered by this privacy policy.

## How long is the Information Kept?

"The Owners" will only keep the personal information for so long as it is useful. At the conclusion of such time, "The Owners" will delete this information.

## Submitted Sites

If you submit a website to this directory then you are agreeing to allow "The Owners" to make any or all parts of the information you enter publicly available (excluding your email address). Where applicable this clause supersedes any other clause within this document that may be in conflict with it.

## Additional Information

This site contains links to other sites. "The Owners" are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of these sites.

We reserve the right to make changes to the privacy policy at any time. Please check back from time to time to ensure that you are aware of these changes.

Any questions relating to this privacy policy may be sent through our contact page.
